A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1967-1968
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1967-1968
  - University Center in Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - Universities Research Association 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - University Hall 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - University Houses 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - University Houses - Faulkner 1967-1968 (Box 67)
  - Virginia Legislative Advisory Council 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - University Press of Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - University Printing Office 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - University Relations [see also Public Relations] 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - Upward Bound 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Education Facilities 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Virginia Education Association 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - Visitors - general 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Awards 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Buildings and Grounds 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Educational Policy 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Executive Committee 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Finance Committee 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Mary Washington College 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Medical Committee 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Student Affairs and Athletics 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Special Committee, Recognition of Benefactors of U.Va. 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Docket, October 1967 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Minutes, October 1967 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Docket, December 1967 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Minutes, December 1967 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Docket, February 1968 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Minutes, February 1968 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Docket, April 1968 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Minutes, April 1968 1967-1968 (Box 70)
  - Visitors - Docket, June 1968 1967-1968 (Box 72)
  - Visitors - Minutes, June 1968 1967-1968 (Box 72)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 72)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 72)
  - Walpole Society 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - Wheeler Bennett, Sir John 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - Woman, Dean of 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - YMCA 1967-1968 (Box 73)